Translated by Releska
The sky that shines in the dark sky
It's a day, so let's go and get a picnic
Of course, you are always with you
I have a lot of experience in this world
That's right, happy, and I can't be with you
I'm not a good boy, but I'm happy
I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy
You and me, you and me, you too
If I love you, I'll be with you
I'm just looking for you!
I really do love you so much!
Ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah.
Not at all, not at all!
After we explored the town and there were a lot of things that happened to us,
we broke up with the world that is so different from ours.
I wonder where we are,
why we can't even look back in the world that we were all alone...
But I didn't start the game.
I was so excited to become a family member of my family!
And I was so excited to be together with my friends!
Today's dish is a new dish!
Good morning! Good morning!
Good morning!
You're doing great with delicious dishes!
You're making a sweet potato!
Good morning!
It's a sweet potato!
It's a potato potato!
Hey!
It looks cute, isn't it?
No, it's not that bad.
Thank you for the ride.
See you again.
Dad, you don't have a little more jump than Ringo.
Oh, I see.
It's a pretty good performance.
Oh, it's a penalty.
It's a penalty.
Are you feeling good?
Good, good.
If you're busy all day, you'll get sick.
Come on.
Oh, what's wrong with you?
Why don't you take care of it?
Hey, since you came to this world,
you don't have to worry about me at all.
Huh?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm worried about something.
I've been here for a long time.
I've been here for years.
What's wrong with you?
Well, in this world,
I'm going to continue my business.
It may be a little difficult.
If you do that, you have to do something more.
I said that.
I'm worried about it.
I can't do something more.
I see.
What are you doing here?
I'm at a pet shop.
A pet?
It's a rare animal.
There's a lot in it, right?
There's a pet shop too.
There's no pet shop.
It's not like that.
It's not a pet shop or a pet shop.
But I don't want to sell it.
Then what do you want to sell it?
That's why.
I want to sell it.
I'm going to sell it.
Huh?
I'm not going to sell it because I have a kid.
Don't be too selfish.
That...
That's...
That's what I'm going to do!
I'm going to sell it because I have a kid.
I...
I'll show you the first pet shop in Japan.
What's wrong, father?
You ate something weird.
I'm worried.
I was worried that I couldn't go to this village.
I decided to go to work as a father.
I see. My father became a carpenter.
I'll give you a lesson.
What should I do?
That's why...
I haven't thought about it yet.
I'll do it anyway.
Look at me.
I'll show you how to make a pet shop.
I'll explain how to make a pet shop.
That's not true.
What's wrong?
Your father became a carpenter.
That's not true.
Now, it's done.
It's not wrong.
Hey, Muka Muka!
I thought about it, but I quit.
I'll do whatever you want.
Erika, let's eat.
It's not right.
But it's not right.
Is it right?
What's this?
It's a trap.
I thought it was a trap.
But what should I do?
It's a trap.
What's wrong?
Now, it's all right.
I'll make a pet shop.
What?
It's the same as the animals.
The shadows and the humans.
It's not right.
I found the work of a pet shop.
I see.
What?
Is it a trap?
Is it a trap or a trap?
I can do it.
It's all right.
She Gordon is the common place.
Since she has a strong mind, she got it back.
She is the common place.
Because of the ground you have to dig it.
But if you dig it up with your st elections,
It'll hurt you.
That's right.
I went to this shelter to meet many people.
Look at the organization!
You'll run off.
I asked you from Donoku.
Are you worried about me?
Right.
Where's the truth?
The head!
The service is over. Why are you going?
We've been able to get a lot of energy from here.
We've been able to get energy from here.
And one day, we'll have a lot of energy.
So we need to be able to get energy from the foot.
We're not taking care of our energy and getting energy from our body.
Ahh!
Ahhhh!
What should we do?
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sure that's why I'm worried about girls.
But can I do that?
I can do it!
What? Really?
I'm sure you're right, too.
I'll be right next to you when I make a promise.
Ha ha ha!
I'm so tired!
Thank you so much!
What are you saying?
Huh?
Did you get angry when you got angry?
Yeah, but...
That's a good thing.
Thank you so much!
Huh?
You're really annoying.
Really?
Oh, I'm so tired!
What the hell is that?
I can't eat it properly.
I'm sorry.
Okay, I'll go to the waiting room.
Oh, thank you.
I'm sure you're right.
Yeah, I'm sure you're right.
Good luck.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's it.
I forgot to bring that one.
I can't wait to see you again.
Good luck.
Yeah, thank you!
Yeah.
Let's go first.
It's a service night, isn't it?
Yeah.
What is that?
Mr. Chotan, do you guys remember that chair?
That's because you'rebrake's stomach.
You were really kind.
What is that?
Tell me, sir.
What?
Go! Go!
Go!
My head is shaking so much that I can't stand it.
Look at this.
This is a promise to Geli.
There was a promise like this.
Father, if this is it,
I'll give you the best weapon.
Yes.
Yo-chan.
What did you do today?
We have five hours to go.
It's a country.
Is there a new one?
Yes, well.
The price of the food is already very high.
It's a big deal.
Roku sent it to me from the sky.
That's not true, Roku.
I'll give it to you.
I'm so happy that you can give it to everyone.
That's right.
I'm so grateful to everyone.
Hey, are you hungry?
Yes, I'm hungry too.
I'm hungry too.
Hey!
What are you doing here?
My head is shaking so much.
Yes, I'm hungry.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
I'm hungry too.
Good.
Father, thank you for your hard work.
The weapon is finished.
It's the price of our strength.
I'm hungry too.
Help me, Roku.
Father, thank you.
Are you going to be a child?
I'm hungry too.
I ate lunch.
When I came home, I ate all the food we had.
I'm hungry too.
If I drink this, I'll be hungry soon.
I can't go.
I'm sleepy.
Good.
It looks like it's getting dark.
It's getting dark.
I'm hungry too.
We want to eat too much.
Are you hungry?
If you're hungry, you must be hungry too.
I have the language of the old-fashioned, but I'm hungry too.
I'm hungry too.
If you're hungry, you must be hungry too.
Okay, Gogi, I'm hungry too.
I'm hungry too.
Oh, I'm getting a lot of attention!
Oh, I see. We were so great together.
If I were to come a bit closer, I wouldn't sleep quickly.
Hey, hey, hey.
We'll take the rest of the food to our staff.
We're going to have lunch.
There's a lot of food in there.
It's been a while.
Wait.
I was worried about you.
I'm glad.
But you're too lazy.
When I was a kid, I was impressed.
If you were a kid, I wouldn't be able to thank you.
I want to ask you a favor right now.
Do you want to be impressed?
That's right.
That's not good.
Even if you don't get it right now,
you'll get the feeling of being touched by you.
That's right.
That's not good.
You're right.
It's been a while.
Hurry up and give it to me.
But, Hazuki-chan.
I can't go with you.
I'll go with you.
Everyone, if you're not interested,
hurry up and give it to me.
I'll take care of you.
I'm not a bad guy.
You're right.
I'm so scared.
Do you feel okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry for the pain.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
That's right.
There's no way you're getting hurt.
Don't worry about that.
The garbage you put in is dangerous.
It's kind of dangerous.
A lot of people just look at you.
It's getting a little bit.
What's wrong?
I'm just a little bit thirsty.
See you tomorrow.
Well, I worked hard.
Oh, I can't fit.
Mr. Dost will be home.
Are you going home?
Do you want to go home?
I...I don't have anything like that. Please do it slowly.
Oh, I feel like I'm in the room right now. I can't stand it. I can't stand it.
Stop it!
What? What's wrong with you?
If you don't want to get out of the car, your head will get stuck in the car.
What?
If that's the case, you can go home.
Oh, I feel like my head is still stuck in the car.
It's okay, it's okay.
Are you still in the car?
Yes.
If you want to get out of the car, don't you want to go home?
Well, go home with that guy.
That's why I don't want to go home.
What are you saying?
If you want to go home by yourself, don't you want to go home?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Your head is getting better.
Are you still in the car?
Yes.
I said it now.
Go home with that guy!
Why are you so angry?
This is not what you want.
What's wrong with you?
Stop it!
Hey, what's wrong with you, Uiba?
Yeah, I was tired, so I'll go home first.
I'm home.
You were tired, didn't you?
Um, are you all right?
Yeah, I thought I wanted to see you.
I wonder if you're with me.
That's right.
I wonder if you know where I'm going.
Yeah, I'll ask you. Go home!
Hey, hey, hey.
You're so tall!
Then, what's wrong with you?
I didn't expect you to be so tall.
I see.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to bother you.
I'm glad.
I'm worried about you.
Uiba became a big fan of you.
I don't know what to do with you.
What?
You've got to be more careful.
I'm going to be careful.
I'll be careful.
Huh?
I'm scared.
What's wrong?
Hurry!
I'm here!
We don't have to go anywhere since we're born, right?
I don't know where we are.
I don't know.
No.
I don't think the heat is going to get cold.
I wonder if it's still hot in here.
I think it's good for the air.
I know it's good for the air.
I don't know.
Huh!?
Huh?
What!?
Oh my...
What's that?
She's finally able to handle the crisis.
Ah...
That's not when we were close enough to get to the station.
Yeah.
Goji Goji-san!
It's the same as the same!
Thank you!
It's good.
Good, isn't it?
Yeah.
How about you?
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's all right.
Good!
Hey, can you help me out?
Yeah, sure. I'll be right back.
Wow!
I'm so sorry! Wait a minute!
If I eat rice, I won't be able to help you.
It's okay. I won't be able to help you out.
Hey, can you help me out?
Yeah, sure.
I won't be able to help you out.
It's okay.
Yeah, sure.
Hey, can you help me out?
Whee!
A natural artist, a friend like Toru Yuhima has been singing and singing,
but he's really jealous of everyone!
I wonder how he'll be able to show up.
Have you already read it?
Really, is he that kind of a member?
Next time on GOMKAPARA,
we'll be looking forward to a big campus!